<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
 <rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>iam.solostyle.net</title>
    <link>http://iam.solostyle.net/</link>
    <description>Me.</description>
    <language>en-us</language><item><title>Site redesign coming soon</title><link>http://iam.solostyle.net/</link><description>Two-thirty a.m. is a pretty lonely hour, one that I don't see on the clock often, especially when I must wake up three-and-a-half hours later. Yesterday evening was usurped by website redesign plans. When bedtime rolled around, it was still too early for the ideas that had just awakened. I tossed in</description><dc:creator></dc:creator><dc:date>2009-03-10T19:28:00Z</dc:date><guid isPermaLink="true">http://iam.solostyle.net/entry.php?id=tag:iam.solostyle.net,2009-03-10:/2009/03/site-redesign-coming-soon</guid></item><item><title>Lessons of a healer</title><link>http://iam.solostyle.net/</link><description>I learned some good lessons yesterday, as well. Sharon and Dr. Rugg share an office space with a group of physical therapists called Midwest Physical Therapy. The therapist who works there the most, maybe he is the only employee, is kind of an annoying character. One of his patients, a woman who was</description><dc:creator></dc:creator><dc:date>2009-03-07T14:21:00Z</dc:date><guid isPermaLink="true">http://iam.solostyle.net/entry.php?id=tag:iam.solostyle.net,2009-03-07:/2009/03/lessons-of-a-healer</guid></item><item><title>Recipe for body maintenance</title><link>http://iam.solostyle.net/</link><description>Yesterday I saw Dr. Rugg and Sharon again for the now monthly check-ups. It's amazing to realize that it took eleven months to diminish my need for adjustments from twice a week to once a month. As Dr. Rugg said, there worse things to be resigned to than a life of exercise. For the month of February</description><dc:creator></dc:creator><dc:date>2009-03-07T13:47:00Z</dc:date><guid isPermaLink="true">http://iam.solostyle.net/entry.php?id=tag:iam.solostyle.net,2009-03-07:/2009/03/recipe-for-body-maintenance</guid></item><item><title>I need magnesium</title><link>http://iam.solostyle.net/</link><description>Eesh. Everything feels like it's going too slow. I feel like my brain is going too fast!

I jogged and/or ran to the gym, lifted weights, and walked and/or lunged back. The weather is kissably sweet. I want to be outside forever and more.

I keep running into people. It's nice. They all have suc</description><dc:creator></dc:creator><dc:date>2008-09-24T18:38:27Z</dc:date><guid isPermaLink="true">http://iam.solostyle.net/entry.php?id=tag:iam.solostyle.net,2008-09-24:/2008/09/i-need-magnesium</guid></item><item><title>Performance</title><link>http://iam.solostyle.net/</link><description>i had my first performance review today, and apparently i'm off to great start in my career. i expect no less from myself. even if it's something i don't like, if it's something i have decided to do anyway, i must excel. yeah i wonder why it took me this long to verbalize it, but it feels natural to</description><dc:creator></dc:creator><dc:date>2008-08-15T21:20:20Z</dc:date><guid isPermaLink="true">http://iam.solostyle.net/entry.php?id=tag:iam.solostyle.net,2008-08-15:/2008/08/performance</guid></item><item><title>Another Quick Note</title><link>http://iam.solostyle.net/</link><description>Yesterday morning I jogged to the gym and lifted weights. I could bench press more than usual, even though I hadn't pumped iron in a week. When I say bench press, I mean with individual weights, not the bar. I normally do 20 lbs on each side, but yesterday I could do 25 lbs. I did 20 lbs at 10 (or w</description><dc:creator></dc:creator><dc:date>2008-08-11T04:25:32Z</dc:date><guid isPermaLink="true">http://iam.solostyle.net/entry.php?id=tag:iam.solostyle.net,2008-08-11:/2008/08/another-quick-note</guid></item><item><title>A Quick Note</title><link>http://iam.solostyle.net/</link><description>Weeks ago, when I did the static wall splits, I couldn't hold it for more than 15 or 20 seconds. Some time later, I tried it again but more intensely. I focused very hard, cheered myself on, and felt an enormous pop in my right hip. After that, it was sore but relieved. After that time, I could hold</description><dc:creator></dc:creator><dc:date>2008-08-02T12:22:01Z</dc:date><guid isPermaLink="true">http://iam.solostyle.net/entry.php?id=tag:iam.solostyle.net,2008-08-02:/2008/08/a-quick-note</guid></item>  </channel></rss>